bleachportal.net 2014-01-14

# Bleach Portal Â» Jump into the Bleach Anime/Manga with Bleach Portal!

## Bleach Portal: No Better Bleach Source Than This

Site Closed 

#### Privacy Policy:

## Introduction

The following webpage outlines BleachPortal.net's collection and use of personal information from it's users. BleachPortal.net values the privacy of our members and users, we will never share any personal information of anyone who logs on to BleachPortal.net with any 3rd Partys (meaning anyone outside of the BleachPortal.net staff). This includes your e-mail address, name, and location. Upon logging on to BleachPortal.net such things as your IP address and hostname are logged for statistical and security reasons. 

## Cookies:

A cookie is a very small text file placed on your system upon logging on to BleachPortal.net (and most other websites). This file serves as your identification card and is uniquely yours, and can only be read by the server that gave it to you. Cookies tell us that you have returned to a specific web page on BleachPortal.net and help us track your preferences and transactional habits. The basic function of cookies is to help our server remember who you are, editing cookie givin by BleachPortal.net will only work against you.

## Children's Privacy:

BleachPortal.net does not knowingly collect personal data from children under the age of 13. We make reasonable efforts to prevent someone who is underage from joining as a member of BleachPortal.net, and will not collect information from them. If BleachPortal.net learns that a child under the age of 13 has become a member, we will close that child's account and delete any information collected about the child.

Not withstanding the foregoing, BleachPortal.net may choose to retain some personal information such as the child's e-mail address as a means to prevent the child from re-registering at our website. The Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) went into effect in April 2000, and as a result websites all over the world wide web had to change their standards to not collect any information from a child.

## Disclosing Information:

BleachPortal.net may store and disclose personal information allowed or required by applicable law or when deemed advisable by us. This means that we may make disclosures that are necessary to conform to legal and regulatory requirements or processes and to protect the rights, safety, and property of BleachPortal.net, users of the BleachPortal.net website, and the public.

## Security:

At BleachPortal.net we make reasonable efforts to protect personal information such as passwords and use technology such as encryption, access control procedures, firewalls, and physical security. We urge you to use a unique password with both letters and numbers to protect your account on BleachPortal.net and it's affiliated websites. If others, including family, friends or other household members access and use the message board through your login credentials, you are responsible for the actions of that individual. Only in extreme cases will your account be fully terminated.

## Third Partys:

Third Party websites may collect information from users of BleachPortal.net, this information will include your IP address, hostname, and information about your system to help us serve you better. These are purely used for statistical reasons, and will not be used in any way other then that. Some programs that may collect this information include: (BleachPortal.net currently does not accept the use of third partys)

## Website Policy Changes:

BleachPortal.net reserves the right to change this, and any other policy located on our website at anytime without notifying our users. If you have any comments, questions, or concerns regaurding this policy, or any other policy you may send them to us at nination@gmail.net. If the policy stated something at the time you made a transaction that was not carried out until the poilicy changed, your transaction will go by the policy at the time and date you made it.

By continuing to access BleachPortal.net and any of it's affiliated websites and files, you are expressly and impliedly agreeing to all of the terms as stated above on this document. You also hereby affirm that you are in compliance with all Federal, State and Local laws in your place of residence concerning the contents of BleachPortal.net, and are also in agreeance with our Disclaimer and Terms of Use.
